<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour guide Application</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Touristic</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Shopping</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Food</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Hotels</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="disc">Description</string>
    <string name="n1TouristicName">المتحف المصري</string>
    <string name="n1TouristicDisc">المتحف المصري هو أحد أكبر وأشهر المتاحف العالمية، يقع في قلب العاصمة المصرية "القاهرة" بالجهة الشمالية لميدان التحرير. يعود تاريخ إنشائه إلى عام 1835 وكان موقعه حينها بحديقة الأزبكية، حيث ضم وقتها عدداً كبيراً من الآثار المتنوعة، ثم نقل بمحتوياته إلى قاعة العرض الثانية بقلعة صلاح الدين، حتى فكر عالم المصريات الفرنسي أوجوست مارييت الذي كان يعمل بمتحف اللوفر في افتتاح متحفٍ يعرض فيه مجموعة من الآثار على شاطئ النيل عند بولاق، وعندما تعرضت هذه الآثار لخطر الفيضان تم نقلها إلى ملحق خاص بقصر الخديوي إسماعيل بالجيزة، ثم جاء عالم المصريات جاستون ماسبيرو وافتتح عام 1902 في عهد الخديوي عباس حلمي الثاني مبنى المتحف الجديد في موقعه الحالي في قلب القاهرة. يعتبر المتحف المصري من أوائل المتاحف في العالم التي أسست لتكون متحف عام على عكس المتاحف التي سبقته، يضم المتحف أكثر من 180 ألف قطعة أثرية أهمها المجموعات الأثرية التي عثر عليها في مقابر الملوك والحاشية الملكية للأسرة الوسطى في دهشور عام 1894، ويضم المتحف الآن أعظم مجموعة أثرية في العالم تعبر عن جميع مراحل التاريخ المصري القديم.</string>
    <string name="n1TouristicAd">‏ميدان التحرير، القاهرة، مصر</string>
    <string name="n2TouristicName">وادي الملوك</string>
    <string name="n2TouristicDisc">وادي الملوك ويعرف أيضا باسم "وادي بيبان الملوك"، هو واد في مصر استخدم على مدار 500 سنة خلال الفترة ما بين القرنين السادس عشر والحادي عشر قبل الميلاد لتشييد مقابر لفراعنة ونبلاء الدولة الحديثة الممتدة خلال عصور الآسرات الثامنة عشر وحتى الأسرة العشرين بمصر القديمة، ويقع الوادي على الضفة الغربية لنهر النيل في مواجهة طيبة بقلب مدينة طيبة الجنائزية القديمة. وينقسم وادي الملوك إلى واديين؛ الوادي الشرقي والوادي الغربي. وباكتشاف حجرة الدفن الأخيرة عام 2006 والمعروفة باسم علاوة على اكتشاف مدخلين آخرين لنفس الحجرة خلال عام 2008، وصل عدد المقابر المكتشفة حتى الآن إلى 63 مقبرة متفاوتة الأحجام إذ تتراوح ما بين حفرة صغيرة في الأرض وحتى مقبرة معقدة التركيب تحوي أكثر من 120 حجرة دفن بداخلها. استخدمت هذه المقابر جميعها في دفن ملوك وأمراء الدولة الحديثة بمصر القديمة بالإضافة إلى بعض النبلاء ومن كان على علاقة بالأسرة الحاكمة في ذلك الوقت. وتتميز المقابر الملكية باحتوائها على رسومات ونقوش من الميثولوجيا المصرية القديمة توضح العقائد الدينية والمراسم التأبينية في ذلك الوقت. وجميع القبور المكتشفة قد تم فتحها ونهبها في العصور القديمة وعلى الرغم من ذلك بقت دليلا دامغا على قوة ورخاء ملوك ذلك الزمان.</string>
    <string name="n2TouristicAd">يقع الوادي على الضفة الغربية لنهر النيل في مواجهة طيبة (الأقصر حاليا)</string>
    <string name="n3TouristicName">أهرامات الجيزة</string>
    <string name="n3TouristicDisc">مجمع أهرامات الجيزة هو موقع أثري على هضبة الجيزة، على مشارف القاهرة، مصر. ويشمل الأهرامات الثلاثة الكبرى، وأبو الهول العظيم، وعدة مقابر، وقرية عمالية ومجمع صناعي. يقع في الصحراء الغربية، على بعد حوالي 9 كم غرب نهر النيل في البلدة القديمة في الجيزة، وحوالي 13 كم جنوب غرب مركز مدينة القاهرة. الأهرامات، التي كانت شائعة تاريخياً كرموز لمصر القديمة في الخيال الغربي، شاعت في الأزمنة الهلنستية، عندما تم ذكر الهرم الأكبر من قبل أنتيباتر الصيداي كأحد عجائب الدنيا السبع في العالم. وهو حتى الآن أقدم عجائب الدنيا والوحيد الذي لا يزال موجودًا.</string>
    <string name="n3TouristicAd">الهرم، الجيزة</string>
    <string name="n4TouristicName">الكرنك</string>
    <string name="n4TouristicDisc">الكرنك أو مجمع معابد الكرنك الذي يُشتهر باسم معبد الكرنك هو مجموعة من المعابد والبنايات والأعمدة، حيث استمرت عمليات التوسع والبناء منذ العصر الفرعونى وتحديدا ملوك الدولة الوسطي حتى العصر الرومانى في الأقصر في مصر على الشط الشرقى. المعبد بُنى للثالوث الإلهى أمون، زوجته الالهة موت وابنهم الاله خونسو؛ ولكل منهم معبد تابع لمجمع معابد الكرنك. أحياناً يعنى السياح والغير متخصصين بمعبد الكرنك فقط المعبد تابع لأمون آى أمون رع.</string>
    <string name="n4TouristicAd">الكرنك، الاقصر</string>
    <string name="n5TouristicName">معبد الاقصر</string>
    <string name="n5TouristicDisc">معبد الأقصر معبد كبير من المعابد المصرية القديمة المعقدة يقع على الضفة الشرقية لنهر النيل في مدينة الأقصر اليوم المعروفة باسم. تأسس سنة 1400 قبل الميلاد. شُيد معبد الأقصر لعبادة آمون رع وزوجته موت وابنهما خونسو؛ وهي الآرباب التي يطلق عليها أيضا لقب الثالوث الطيبي. تم تشييد معبد الأقصر في عهد ملوك الأسرة الثامنة عشر، والأسرة التاسعة عشرة. وأهم الأبنية القائمة بالمعبد هي تلك التي شيدها الملكان أمنحوتب الثالث ورمسيس الثاني. كما أقام الملك تحتمس الثالث مقاصير لزوار ثالوث طيبة المقدس، كما قام توت عنخ آمون باستكمال نقوش جدرانه. وقد دمرت المقصورة الثلاثية التي كانت قد شيدت من قبل في عهد الملكة حتشبسوت والملك تحتمس الثالث ؛ ثم أعيد بناؤها في عهد الملك رمسيس الثاني. سمي المعبد أيضاً "إيبت رسيت". وهو من أحسن المعابد المصرية حفظاً وأجملها بناء، وفيه يتجلى تخطيط المعبد المصري أوضح ما يكون.</string>
    <string name="n5TouristicAd"> مدينة الأقصر</string>
    <string name="n6TouristicName">فيلة</string>
    <string name="n6TouristicDisc">جزيرة فيلة، هي جزيرة في منتصف نهر النيل وهي إحدى الحصون الأقوى على طول حدود مصر الجنوبية، وتفصل النيل إلى قناتين معاكستين في أسوان، كان بها معبد فيلة وانتقل من مكانه الأصلي على جزيرة فيلة وتم تجميعه على جزيرة أجيليكا، وذلك في أعقاب بناء السد العالي. ويرجع اسم فيلة أو فيلاي إلى اللغة الإغريقية التي تعني أو أما الاسم العربي لها فهو أنس الوجود نسبة لأسطورة أنس الموجودة في قصص ألف ليلة وليلة أما الاسم المصري القديم والقبطي فهو بيلاك أو بيلاخ ويعني الحد أو النهاية لأنها كانت آخر حدود مصر في الجنوب. ومجموعة العبادة كرست لعبادة الإلهة إيزيس غير أن الجزيرة احتوت على معابد لحتحور وأمنحتب وغيرها من المعابد.</string>
    <string name="n6TouristicAd"> في منتصف نهر النيل</string>
    <string name="n1ShoppingName">Khan Al Khalili</string>
    <string name="n1ShoppingDisc">This market in the interiors of the old Cairo city is centuries old and is a must-visit for all those who have a bug for shopping. Even if you’re not someone who is into shopping, you can just roam around this market to experience the hustle and bustle of this spectacular Arab city. Keep your pockets filled with cash and learn well to haggle beforehand, as that skill comes very handy at this place. Probably the best place in the entire city to buy novelty T-shirts, little bottles of colored sand having pictures of camels, as well as, the amazing souvenirs with your name printed in hieroglyphics, an ancient Egyptian writing.</string>
    <string name="n1ShoppingAd">Al-Azhar Street, Cairo , Egypt</string>
    <string name="n2ShoppingName">Souk Al Fustat</string>
    <string name="n2ShoppingDisc">Situated just outside the northern entrance to Coptic Cairo, the Souk al Fustat is a fascinating little shopping mall that aims at the clear sighted foreign buyers. Do not miss checking out the beautiful handmade copies of Fatimid as well as Mamluke lamps that are sold here by Hassan and Mohamed. Although the prices here are fixed and no amount of bargaining skills can help you, the items available here are also worth your money. You’ll find everything from wonderful bedouin work on pillowcases, colorful metal cups, woodwork, paintings, traditional, bowls, trays, ceramic products, etc. This adds this market to the list of mystery shopping in Egyptas one gets extremely confused about where to spend their bucks. It is a great place to visit, also because you can dive deep into the interiors of the old Cairo as also pay a visit to the hanging church situated next to the souk.</string>
    <string name="n2ShoppingAd"> Corner el Emam Street and Hassan al Anwar Street | Old Cairo, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n3ShoppingName">Aswan Souk</string>
    <string name="n3ShoppingDisc">This beautiful outdoor market is one of the important places of Aswan, southernmost city of Egypt. And although the city is growing day by day, receiving more and more tourists, this Souk retains all the features and characteristics of a millennia-old crossroads between Africa and the Mediterranean world on its trading routes. One can get good quality spices for very reasonable prices here.</string>
    <string name="n3ShoppingAd"> Aswan, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n4ShoppingName">Old Market</string>
    <string name="n4ShoppingDisc">The best place in Sharm for souvenirs as well as shopping in Egypt , the market boasts of plenty of juice and fruit shops. Also, one can buy things like spices, oils, t-shirts or even small pyramids for keepsakes. Also, there is an extremely beautiful Mosque here which is a must-visit while strolling through the roads of the Old Market. The prices here can be a bit on the higher side, but they are negotiable and one can bargain here. The market also offers plenty of options to eat with many restaurants and shisha lounges.</string>
    <string name="n4ShoppingAd">Sharm El Sheikh, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n5ShoppingName">Souk-Al-Gamaal</string>
    <string name="n5ShoppingDisc">Souk-al-Gamaal or the Birqash Camel Market is a fascinating market in Cairo where one can buy camels for meat, racing or for farming. One of the most horrible sights here is that of the camels who are tied to a rope to keep them from running away, while also being hit with a stick in order to herd them in a specific direction. One can take pictures of the camels here but only after you have paid up for taking your camera inside the market with you.</string>
    <string name="n5ShoppingAd">Barqash, Imbaba, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n6ShoppingName">Sharia Khayamiya</string>
    <string name="n6ShoppingDisc">Located in the Cairo, this market is an amazing place for a stroll as it houses very unique and interesting items. The vendors here are very friendly and kind, unlike most of the vendors in Egypt who irritate you by asking you to buy something from their shop. There are many carpets and shawls on offer, as well as mini-sized tents that serve as play house for the kids here. The materials available here are used for several occasions like weddings.</string>
    <string name="n6ShoppingAd">Islamic Cairo, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n7ShoppingName">Suuq El Ataba</string>
    <string name="n7ShoppingDisc">This amazing market in Cairo has a lot to offer with many options for its visitors. Various types of jewellery, accessories, clothes, antiques, handmade crafts, etc are available here so there’s at least something for everyone who visits here, making it a must-visit for everyone visiting the beautiful country of Egypt. The atmosphere here is brilliant and one can easily mix with the locals here and share your life experiences too as they are very welcoming which makes it the best place to shop in Egypt. With the prices being very reasonable, there is no need to bargain as you are already getting all the items for the least amount of money. Thus, the market boasts of being one of Egypt’s cheapest markets.</string>
    <string name="n7ShoppingAd">Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n8ShoppingName">Luxor Bazaar</string>
    <string name="n8ShoppingDisc">Situated in the Luxor Center in Luxor, this beautiful market offers things like scarves, statues of deities, music CD’s, gold, silver, clothes as well as spices. The entrance to the market is marked by a structure that looks like a gate that leading to a medieval castle. All the shops here, have matching signs. Also on offer here, are leather goods, papyrus, and postcards. You need a lot of hassling skills in order to buy things at cheap prices here.</string>
    <string name="n8ShoppingAd">Luxor Center, Luxor, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n9ShoppingName">Cairo Festival City Mall</string>
    <string name="n9ShoppingDisc">The perfect shopping place for all ages and sizes, this spectacular mall in the city of Cairo is one of the country’s best. One can get all the necessary household things as well as shop from some of the world’s best brands. And if you get tired or hungry while shopping, there are numerous restaurants here serving delicious food as well. With a lot of shops under one roof, this is the place you should visit whilst your visit to the beautiful country.</string>
    <string name="n9ShoppingAd">Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n1foodName">Sequoia</string>
    <string name="n1foodDisc">The great vibes and stunning view of this place is still unmatched anywhere else in the city. You’re basically surrounded by the Nile from all angles. Their menu is very diverse and they serve alcoholic beverages and shisha. What more could you ask for?</string>
    <string name="n1foodAd">Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n2foodName">Andrea</string>
    <string name="n2foodDisc">This is a personal favourite of mine. It takes after the famous Marryoteya one and the food is to die for. The grilled chicken, chicken liver and Kobeba are a must try! You can get your name customized in a sand bottle, watch your bread being baked the old-school way over the coals or take a donkey ride. Yes, you read that right.</string>
    <string name="n2foodAd"> New Giza, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n3foodName">Il Piccolo Mondo</string>
    <string name="n3foodDisc">This is one of Le Pacha boat’s classics. They serve authentic Italian food the right way! The restaurant design imitates the Piazza San Carlo in Italy which makes it quite unique. You can even write a note or make a drawing on the walls, that are already covered in writings from previous customers, and leave a memory that will last a lifetime.</string>
    <string name="n3foodAd">Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n4foodName"> Tabla LUNA</string>
    <string name="n4foodDisc">This Maadi restaurant features colourful, vibrant interiors with Aztec and Mayan inspired floor tiles. It is the first Latin American restaurant of its kind in Egypt. Tabla LUNA has established itself in Cairo for its very creative and super delicious dishes. There’s nowhere else in Cairo where you can get a mango filled with white chocolate flan.</string>
    <string name="n4foodAd"> Maadi, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n5foodName">Abou El Sid</string>
    <string name="n5foodDisc">This is a Cairo classic. Make sure you head to the original branch in Zamalek and transport back to Egypt in the 1940s. Abou El Sid offers a full blown Egyptian culinary experience ranging from Molokheya with rabbits to pigeons to Om Ali.</string>
    <string name="n5foodAd">Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n6foodName">Naguib Mahfouz Cafe</string>
    <string name="n6foodDisc">This authentic Egyptian cafe and restaurant in Khan El Khalili is definitely worth a visit. Not only is the food delicious (the feteer is to die for), but the live oud band entertainment also gives this place a very lively authentic atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="n6foodAd">Khan El Khalili, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n7foodName"> Maison Thomas</string>
    <string name="n7foodDisc">This will forever be one of our favourites. This brick oven pizzeria has been around since 1922 and has since served up the most amazing thin crusted pizza with fresh, yummy ingredients. We recommend the Marinara or Hot Dog Pizza.</string>
    <string name="n7foodAd">Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n8foodName">OAK Grill</string>
    <string name="n8foodDisc">This fancy-pants restaurant in Conrad Hotel, even though slightly overpriced, is well worth a visit, at least as a one time thing to celebrate your partner’s birthday or your recent promotion. We highly recommend the rib-eye steak and the vanilla bean crème brulèe.</string>
    <string name="n8foodAd">Conrad Hotel, Nile Corniche, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n9foodName"> L’Asiatique</string>
    <string name="n9foodDisc">This is another Le Pacha classic, which also recently opened in 6 October. It was chosen as Africa’s best restaurant years in a row a few years back and it truly is worthy of the title. This sleek and secluded restaurant serves up some of the best sushi and Pan-Asian cuisine in town, so dress up and head down there with your family and friends for a dinner to remember.</string>
    <string name="n9foodAd">Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n1hotelName">Fairmont Nile City</string>
    <string name="n1hotelDis">A melting pot of history and diversity, the city of Cairo is ideal for both business and leisure. Like the city itself, Fairmont Nile City offers a delightful series of contrasts, combining advanced technology and modern design with local flavors and flair. With sweeping panoramas of the river Nile and the Pyramids in the distance, Cairo’s beauty and history are always in sight from your luxury accommodation. During your stay, embark on culinary adventures at the city’s finest restaurants, enjoy the fresh air at our rooftop poolside restaurant and pamper yourself at Willow Stream Spa. Part of the prestigious Nile City complex, this luxury hotel is the perfect location for business events. The space consists of 845 square meters (9,100 square feet) plus 450 square meters (4,800 square feet) of outdoor space dedicated to meetings and conventions, comprising of 10 meeting rooms including a ballroom. The space also offers spectacular river Nile views.</string>
    <string name="n1hotelAd">Nile City Towers, Corniche El Nil Ramlet Beaulac, Cairo,Egypt</string>
    <string name="n2hotelName">Le Passage Cairo</string>
    <string name="n2hotelDis">Le Passage Cairo Hotel and Casino is located in Heliopolis, an elegant business and residential district in Cairo and it is considered one of the safest area in town. The hotel is only five minutes from Cairo International Airport and ten minutes from the Cairo International Convention Centre and Fair Grounds, with free shuttle bus service, free wifi and free internet. Great design is the key to this urban, cosmopolitan business and leisure base, providing a sophisticated and stylish environment in the throbbing heart of Egypt and the Middle East. Le Passage Cairo Hotel and Casino celebrates individuality with a wide range of accommodation choices from well appointed rooms and suites with exquisite views to the Executive Club floor which is ideal for business travelers, short breaks, family holidays or those special occasions.</string>
    <string name="n2hotelAd">Cairo International Airport Road El Horreya-Heliopolis, Cairo 11511 Egypt</string>
    <string name="n3hotelName">Sofitel Cairo Nile El Gezirah</string>
    <string name="n3hotelDis">On the southern tip of Gezirah Island, the hotel is a corner of paradise in central Cairo, minutes from Cairo’s business districts. Discover a haven of peace during a vacation in Egypt, and a comfortable base to rest after a successful day of business. Relax by the pool, pamper yourself in Sofitel SPA, wine and dine in our international restaurants and bars. Surrender to luxury and come for a day, a weekend, a week…or more. A stroll along the hotel’s lush riverside promenade takes you to a host of acclaimed restaurants and bars. You can take your time, enjoying the cool shade of exotic palms and breathing in the scent of hibiscus. You’ll hear the gentle sound of water lapping as you rest on a Nile-side terrace with a cool drink, and dine on international cuisine. It’s especially beautiful at dusk, when the sun sets over Cairo’s skyline and vibrant nightlife. Escape the city for a day at our secluded Cairo hotel, which feels like an exclusive Egyptian resort set in lush gardens. Take advantage of Sofitel SPA and Sofitel FIT, float in an infinity pool overlooking the Nile, unwind in a bubbling whirlpool bath… whatever you desire. Day membership includes discounts to the restaurants and bars which line the Nile-side promenade, promising refreshment and fun for families, couples and friends.</string>
    <string name="n3hotelAd">3 El Thawra Council St Zamalek, Cairo 11511 Egypt</string>
    <string name="n4hotelName">Le Meridien Cairo Airport</string>
    <string name="n4hotelDis">Your Gateway to Egypt Discovery. Le Méridien Cairo Airport offers 66 club floor rooms with a dedicated club lounge, 264 deluxe rooms, 9 studio suites, 9 panoramic deluxe suites and 1 presidential suite - all inside of Cairo airport. All rooms and suites are fully soundproofed, smoke-free, and feature the Le Méridien signature beds. The refined and modern design creates a perfectly relaxed experience. A combination of complimentary WIFI + cable connection coupled with the latest technology makes it easy to conduct business if necessary.</string>
    <string name="n4hotelAd">3 Cairo International Airport, Terminal Cairo International Airport, Terminal 3, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n5hotelName">Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir</string>
    <string name="n5hotelDis">Finding an ideal family-friendly hotel in Cairo does not have to be difficult. Welcome to Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir, a nice option for travelers like you. While staying at Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir, visitors can check out Zamalek (Gezira Island) (0.5 mi) and Mosque of Al-Azhar (0.6 mi), some of Cairo top attractions. Guest rooms offer amenities such as a flat screen TV, air conditioning, and a minibar, and guests can go online with free wifi offered by the hotel. Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir features a 24 hour front desk, a concierge, and room service, to help make your stay more enjoyable. The property also boasts a pool and breakfast. If you are driving to Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir, parking is available. Cairo has plenty of Korean restaurants. So when you’re here, be sure to check out popular spots like Gaya Restaurant, Hana, and Zentro, which are serving up some great dishes. During your visit, be sure to check out popular attractions like Cairo Tower (0.7 mi) and Citadel (Al-Qalaa) (1.2 mi), which are all within walking distance of the hotel. Steigenberger Hotel El Tahrir looks forward to welcoming you on your visit to Cairo.</string>
    <string name="n5hotelAd">2 Kasr El Nile St Tahrir Square, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n6hotelName">Ramses Hilton</string>
    <string name="n6hotelDis">Finding an ideal family-friendly hotel in Cairo does not have to be difficult. Welcome to Ramses Hilton, a nice option for travelers like you. Given the close proximity of popular landmarks, such as Zamalek (Gezira Island) (0.5 mi) and Mosque of Al-Azhar (0.9 mi), guests of Ramses Hilton can easily experience some of Cairo most well known attractions. Ramses Hilton is a family-friendly hotel offering a flat screen TV, a minibar, and air conditioning in the rooms, and it is easy to stay connected during your stay as free wifi is offered to guests. The hotel features a concierge, room service, and a rooftop terrace. Plus, guests can enjoy a pool and free breakfast, which have made this a popular choice among travelers visiting Cairo. For guests with a vehicle, parking is available. While you’re here, be sure to check out some of the cafes, including Naguib Mahfouz Cafe, Hard Rock Cafe Cairo/Citadel, and El Fishawi, all of which are a short distance from Ramses Hilton. Cairo is also home to Military Museum, a popular military museum that is not too far from Cairo Hilton. Ramses Hilton looks forward to welcoming you on your visit to Cairo.</string>
    <string name="n6hotelAd">Corniche El Nile 1115, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n7hotelName">Cairo Marriott Hotel</string>
    <string name="n7hotelDis">Among premier Cairo, Egypt hotels, Cairo Marriott Hotel and Omar Khayyam Casino sits in the Zamalek area and is the perfect destination for weekend getaways, vacations, and business travel. The twin towers of this landmark hotel in Cairo rise 20 stories high and provide magnificent views of the Nile and six acres of palace gardens.</string>
    <string name="n7hotelAd">16 Saray El Gezira Street Zamalek, Cairo, Egypt</string>
    <string name="n8hotelName">Al Masa Hotel</string>
    <string name="n8hotelDis">You are invited to escape the noise and the pollution and to enjoy the peaceful atmosphere on Al Masa spectacular heights. While sitting under a pergola surrounded by the stunning nature enjoy beverage of choice that are served to match the moment. It is the spot for a quiet, contemplative moment where you can enjoy the tranquility of the environment. In a one-of-a-kind experience, imagine your self-hiking along one of the most beautiful ridge walks in the green foothills. Al Masa Hotel features a terrace with a swimming pool. In the green area of Nasr City, it includes 5 restaurants and a spa center. All the elegant rooms have a balcony. Al Masa Hotel has a selection of activities, including different types of massages, Billiards, cinema and bowling. Cairo International Airport is a 10-minute drive and Cairo International Conference Centre is just a 5-minute drive away. The center of Cairo and the Egyptian Museum are both 20 minutes away by car.</string>
    <string name="n8hotelAd">Abdel Aziz El Shennawy St Behind The Stage, Nasr City, Cairo 11511 Egypt</string>
    <string name="n9hotelName">Sonesta Hotel</string>
    <string name="n9hotelDis">The Sonesta Cairo 409 spacious guest rooms and suites offer a variety of luxurious amenities. A room on the executive floors offer exclusive lounges and 24-hour concierge service. The poolside bar and full-service spa with a Turkish steam bath are heavens for relaxation. After the pampering, the hotel offers several options at its gourmet restaurants serving Italian, Lebanese, Japanese, or French cuisine. One of the best Cairo hotels, the Sonesta is ideal for both business and leisure travelers.</string>
    <string name="n9hotelAd">3 El Tayaran Street, Nasr City, Cairo 9039 Egypt</string>
</resources>
